largeanimal.com 2011-05-26

# Privacy Policy | Large Animal Games

## What This Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how Large Animal Games treats personal information that Large Animal Games collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Large Animal Games products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Large Animal Games does not own or control, or to people that Large Animal Games does not employ or manage.

## Information Collection and Use

Large Animal Games collects personal information when you register with Large Animal Games.

When you register we ask for information such as your name and email address. Once you register with Large Animal Games and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

Large Animal Games uses information for the following general purposes: fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, to provide information to third party application developers, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

When you use our Send To a Friend feature: The e-mail address information you provide to us when you use the 'Send To a Friend feature' is used only to customize your greeting with your name and your recipient's name, and to deliver email notifications to you and your recipient. Large Animal Games will not add this e-mail address information to any mailing lists.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Large Animal Games does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Large Animal Games under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Large Animal Games communicate with you about offers from Large Animal Games and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * We are required to disclose any or all information to the extent necessary or appropriate to comply with applicable laws, subpoenas, court orders, legal process served on Large Animal Games or in legal proceedings where Large Animal Games believes such information is relevant or believes in good faith that its disclosure is required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if Large Animal Games is acquired by or merged with another company.

## Cookies

Large Animal Games may set and access Large Animal Games cookies on your computer. Large Animal Games does not allow other companies to access the cookies we set on your computer. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Large Animal Games' cookies.

## Children

Our site is not intended for children under 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If we receive information from anyone who we later learn is under the age of 13, we destroy the information.

## Email Newsletter

Our newsletter is strictly run as an "opt-in" newsletter. We never send unsolicited emails. Information gathered during voluntary player registration is restricted to email address. This information is used solely by Large Animal Games and will not be sold to, or used by, any third party. Large Animal Games will only use this information for sending the newsletter about product updates and new releases.

## Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Large Animal Games reserves the right to amend this policy from time to time. Any amendments to this policy will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof.

## Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at info@largeanimal.com.
